http://www.infinitysw.com/privacy

INFINITYSW.COM STATEMENT OF PRIVACY
At Infinity Softworks, we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete privacy statement.
Collecting your Personal Information
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to register before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, or when purchasing and registering Infinity Softworks products. Personal Information collected by Infinity Softworks often is limited to name, e-mail address, and telephone number but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.
For example: If you choose to make a purchase in the Buy area of the Web site, we will request Personal Information such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number. Credit card numbers are securely submitted to our payment processor at the time of purchase confirmation. AT NO TIME IS YOUR CREDIT CARD NUMBER KEPT IN OUR FILES.
When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase. When you do, we keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site. This is considered your personal profile.
Use of your Personal Information
We use your Personal Information for three primary purposes:
To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Infinity Softworks.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. For instance, this could include sending postal mail promotions or email newsletters. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
Infinity Softworks will disclose your Personal Information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Infinity Softworks or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Infinity Softworks and its family of Web sites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Infinity Softworks, its Web sites, or the public.
Control of your Personal Information
When you register or otherwise give us Personal Information, Infinity Softworks will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.
At any time, you are welcome to contact us and request to be taken out of the contact list.
Infinity Softworks occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services. For email, this is sent by Infinity Softworks on behalf of the partner company or, for postal mail, sent by the partner company with one-time use stickers.
Access to your Personal Information
At any time, you can email Infinity Softworks with current contact information or opt out of email updates.
Security of your Personal Information
Infinity Softworks strictly protects the security of your Personal Information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
Your Personal Information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where Infinity Softworks, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.
Protection of Children’s Personal Information
The Infinity Softworks site does not publish content that is targeted to children.
Use of Cookies
To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want, Infinity Softworks collects aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. In other cases, Infinity Softworks uses cookies for tracking special promotions to ensure that you receive any discounts expected. We do not track individual uses of the site except where outlined in the Use of IP Addresses section below.
When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer’s machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.
Web beacons, also known as clear GIF technology, or action tags, assist in delivering the cookie. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on an infinitysw.com Web page. We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information; it is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about web site usage. We do not share tracking information outside of Infinity Softworks, and do not allow other companies to place clear GIFs on our sites.
If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the infinitysw.com Web site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you may not automatically qualify for special promotions.
Use of IP Addresses
Infinity Softworks does not currently track IP addresses for any purpose.
Changes to this Statement
Infinity Softworks will occasionally update this privacy statement.
Contact Information
Infinity Softworks welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please see contact information by clicking here.
View Site: Mobile | Standard
�1997-2020 Infinity Softworks, Inc.
Terms of Use |
PRIVACY
